Romania Subject Files, Inclusive: 1936-2008, undated, Bulk: 1974-1991
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Denominational, 1936-2008, undated; 2
  - Orthodox Church. Heresy. Cults. Schisms, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Church Statistics, 1972-1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Relations with Fellow Believers, 1964-2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - American Autocephaly of Romanian Orthodox Church, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - American Autocephaly of Romanian Orthodox Church. Trifa, Valerian, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Pan-Orthodox Relations, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Meetings of Orthodox Church, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1975-1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Anglican Church, 1966-1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Armenian Church, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Christian Peace Conference, 1975-1986 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Church of Scotland, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Evangelical Church of Germany, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Greek Catholic Church, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Muslim Believers, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Jewish Believers, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Lutheran Church, 1971-1980 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Old Catholics, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Reformed Church, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Roman Catholic Church, 1974-1999 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Uniate Church, 1972-1999 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations in US, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Orthodox Church's Ecumenical Relations with Vatican, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Orthodox Church and Ecumenical Movement, 1974-1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Orthodox Church's Relations with the World Council of Churches, 1974-1999 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Romanian Orthodox Church in WCC, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Orthodox Church's Relations with European Council of Churches, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Orthodox Religion and National Identity, 1976-1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Orthodox Church Involvement in Secular Affairs and Politics, 1976-1991 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Orthodox Church Art. Architecture. Literature. Music, 1978-2002 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Orthodox Women, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Orthodox Youth and Children, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Church Social and Charity Work, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Church (1 of 2), 1970-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Church (2 of 2), 1977-1991, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Individual Pentecostal Believers. Rascol, Vasile, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Individual Pentecostal Believers. Samu, Ioan, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Church Administration, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Church-State Relations, 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Persecution of Pentecostal Believers, 1976-1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Clergy. Priesthood, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Church's International Contacts, 1968-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Activities Disapproved by State, 1971-1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pentecostal Theological Education, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Pentecostal Church's Relations with Fellow Believers Abroad, 1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Pentecostal Church Architecture. Restoration of Church Buildings, 1975-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Pentecostal Youth and Children, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Reformed Church, 1964-1996, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Reformed Church-State Relations, 1978 1989 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Persecution of Reformed Believers, 1974-1990, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Reformed Church Life, 1986-1999 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Reformed Clergy. Priesthood, 1976-1990 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Individual Reformed Clergy. Tokes, Lazlo (1 of 5), 1989 June-September (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Individual Reformed Clergy. Tokes, Lazlo (2 of 5), 1989 October-November (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Individual Reformed Clergy. Tokes, Lazlo (3 of 5), 1989 December (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Individual Reformed Clergy. Tokes, Lazlo (4 of 5), 1990 January-May (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Individual Reformed Clergy. Tokes, Lazlo (5 of 5), 1990 June-1999 December, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Delegations Visits to Reformed Church, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Reformed Church's Contacts with Foreigners, Émigrés, etc., 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Reformed Church Theological Education, 1983-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Reformed Church Schism, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Reformed Church Statistics, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Reformed Church’s Relations with Fellow Believers, 1989-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Reformed Church Architecture and Restoration, 1989, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. General (1 of 3), 1964-1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church. General (2 of 3), 1978-1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church. General (3 of 3), 1990-1991, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - History of Romanian Roman Catholic Church, 1969-1988 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Believers, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church Administration, 1977-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. State. Law, 1973-1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Persecution of Roman Catholic Believers, 1973-1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Life of Roman Catholic Church, 1978-2002, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy and Priesthood, 1976-1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church Hierarchy, 1978-1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy Ordination. Election. Retirement. Death, etc., 1968-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Clergy, 1967-1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church's International Contacts. Solidarity. Appeals, 1967-1991, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church Activities Disapproved by the State, 1977-1989, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Theology. Philosophy. Ethics, 1966-1987, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church Statistics, 1975-1980, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church's Relations with Fellow Believers (1 of 2), 1977-1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church's Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1976-2001 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church's Relations with Fellow Believers (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church Involvement in Secular Affairs, 1976-1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Youth and Children, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Uniate church. General (1 of 2), 1948-1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Uniate church. General (2 of 2), 1990-2004 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - History of Uniate Church. General, 1948-1982 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - History of Uniate Church. Pre-communist Period, 1977-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - History of Uniate Church. Communist Period, 1977-1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Uniate Church-State Relations, 1976-1987, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Uniate Believers, 1977-1988 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Uniate Believers Fines, 1981-1985 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Uniate Believers Imprisonment, Arrests, Detention, Labor camps, Prison, and Exile, 1971-1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - State Interference in Uniate Church Affairs, 1978-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Uniate Clergy Ordination. Election. Retirement. Death, etc., 1976-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy, 1978-1988, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy. Balan, Ioan, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy. Cristea, Vasile, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy. Dragomir, Ioan, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy. Hossu, Iuliu, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Individual Uniate Clergy. Popan, Flaviu, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Uniate Church’s International Contacts, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Western reactions to Uniate Church Situation, 1973-1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Uniate Church Meetings, Prayer Groups, Rites, Ceremonies, and Services, 1978, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Uniate Believers Protests, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Defense of Uniate Believers' Rights. Litigation, 1977-1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Believers Criticism of Uniate Church Policy, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Uniate Church Theological Education, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Uniate Church’s Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1976-1982 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Uniate Religion and National Identity, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Unitarian Church, 1968-1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)